# **Anish Rijal**

**UI/UX** Designer





# CONTACT INFORMATION

Name: Anish Rijal

Address: 4247 Carlton Way, #3139,

Irving, TX, 75038

Mobile: 214-763-5878

Email: anishrijal10@gmail.com

Languages: English, Nepali, Hindi

Junior UI/UX Developer able to build an App from concept, navigation, layout and programming to UI/UX. Skilled to write well-designed, testable and efficient code using best practices of JavaScript and Angular JS. Excellent at research and time management. Able to manage multiple projects at a time. Ability to solve problems and to learn new things keeps me moving forward.



## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### KSQUARE INC SOLUTIONS. AUGUST 2016 - Present

Position: UI Designer Trainee

Developed a dynamic App from scratch, using Angular Js, JavaScript, HTML. Implemented Node JS solutions for development workflow using Yeoman. Developed other simple JavaScript Application using Require JS, MVC pattern and CSS. Wrote unit tests using Karma and Jasmine.

## Ameriprise Home and Auto Insurance Apr 2015 - Oct 2016

**Position: Junior Dot Net Developer** 

Utilized established development tools, ASP.NET, SQL Server, HTML, CSS, and C#.NET; Designed and tested new Windows and web software applications; Prepared an action plan and identified areas for modification and improvement; Maintained existing software systems by identifying and correcting software defects; Investigated and developed skills in new technologies.

### Department of Labor, Boise, ID Nov 2014 - Jan 2015

**Position: Junior Dot Net Developer** 

Worked on deployment packages for Applications using Visual studio.Net. Experience in SQL Server Database design, Database maintenance, developing SQL queries, stored procedures, and triggers.

**US Army Reserve May 2015 - Present** 



## EDUCATION

May 2014 University of Texas, Arlington

**Bachelor of Applied Mathematics** 

## SKILLS

Overall : JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, Node Js, C#

FrameWorks : Angular Js

Databases : MondoDB, SQL

Methodologies : Scrum